I can hold my own.
I would not say something nice if I didn't think it was really nice.
Well, that's true.
It all seems to mean something to me.
It's just that it's a little bit of hatred already.
It all looks like hatred.
It all looks like hatred to me.
What?
I ran for office, saying I wanted to be in education.
Really? You don't have to be told what to do.
I don't have to worry about that now that it's five-on-five.
I'm looking forward to it.
I see.
Night Tide.
Here we go.
It's a new after-last feed sugar-growing red.
Let's begin immediately, but let's call today's guest.
This is Mr. Idol here.
The morning chime has rung. I, private AV mainstay, am from number 12, Yamanashi Nakayashiko.
Pleased to meet you.
I am Rina Akai from B tube.
Good morning.
How many years has it been since you and Mr. Nakayama met with Mr. Kobayashi and others?
Yes, it has. This year is our 10th anniversary.
This year is your 10th anniversary?
I joined the group when I was 13 years old, and I will turn 23 this year.
Mr. Nakayama, you have turned 23 years old!
I will be 23 years old.
Congratulations!
It's strange to say congratulations.
No, I'm surprised.
Because, you know.
Speaking of Ebichu, you know, it says something about the tour now, and the new member,
Yes.
Because, I feel that you have a strong habit of having older sisters.
That's right. I have five members who are called "elder sister" and five members who are called "younger sister,
I am already a member of the older sister group.
I'm already an older sister, and I'm also a member of the younger sister.
I see, that's how it is. I saw a little bit of your speech today,
It was sold at the convenience store on the day it was recorded today.
That's right.
He said you can go either way.
I can go either way.
This seems to be a bit troubling.
Is it just my own opinion?
I'm just thinking that I'm the one who has to deal with things from the bottom and from the top.
Is there anything like that?
But I am often told that I am in middle management,
It's a lot, isn't it?
Yes, a lot.
Last year, I had a lot of problems,
After the new members, Sakurayama and Nakamura Yuna joined us last December,
I am now looking forward to the new 5-on-5.
Excited?
When Kaho-chan and I joined the group two years ago, we were in charge of educating the three members,
I became their trainer.
You were?
I ran for the position and said I wanted to be a trainer.
Really?
But, as I thought,
You didn't do it because Mr. Maeyama forced you to?
No, no, no.
It's just my own idea.
No, no, no. No, it's not like that. I said I wanted to do it on my own,
I've had opportunities to work with older people, but I've never had a chance to work with younger people,
I didn't really know how to interact with them,
I didn't know how to treat them, so I didn't have much to do.
I didn't know what I could do for them.
That's right.
But Kaho-chan gives her all kinds of advice.
Is that so?
That's right.
I couldn't do it at all, but it's Kaho-chan.
No, no, no. I can see the conversation between the two of you,
But it's a bit emotional for a 23-year-old, isn't it?
Well, you mentioned something like that,
I'm on tour,
We are on tour to rave reviews. Do you enjoy touring? Live performances?
Yes, it's fun. This year was the first time in about 3 years that we had a live show with calls.
How was it? Since when?
We started to lift the ban on call-arounds on the first day of the spring tour in April,
We have set up the setlist accordingly, so it's really fun.
I see.
You seem to have a lot of feelings about the calls, too, don't you?
Not really.
But the setlist allows the fans to give their all.
What?
In other words, the setlist was designed to keep the tension up the whole time.
So, the setlist was something that would be really exciting if it was a call-along.
Yes.
And the whole country.
The whole country is waiting for us.
Kitty, they don't want you.
That's too much to hope for.
Sent to you courtesy of Nana.
Thank you very much.